<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paloma June</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Paloma June</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>## paste this chunk into the ```{r setup} chunk at the top of your project 1 .Rmd file knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE, eval = TRUE, fig.align = &amp;quot;center&amp;quot;, warning = F, message = F, tidy=TRUE, tidy.opts=list(width.cutoff=60), R.options=list(max.print=100)) Introduction
\(~\)
All three datasets used in this project provide data on all the Texas counties. CountyArea.csv provides the land, water, and total area in miles^2 for each Texas county. I chose this dataset because I have always thought the way counties in Texas were shaped and sized were quite arbitrary, and I thought it would be interesting to learn more about the size of Texas counties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project2</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
\(~\)
#install.packages(&amp;quot;Epi&amp;quot;) library(Epi) data(births) library(tidyverse) \(~\)
This data set contains data from 500 singleton births in a London Hospital. It has 8 variables: id, an identification variable for the mother and child; bweight, the birthweight of the child; lowbw, which tracks low birth weight with a value of 1 for babies born below 2500 g and 0 for babies born above; gestwks which which is the gestation period; preterm, which designates whether or not the baby was preterm; matage, the age of the mother; hyp, whether or not the mother had hypertension; and sex 1 for male, 2 for female.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
